Guide to the R. A. (Revels Alcorn) Adams Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 1.34; (1 box)
  - Printed Material (from Series IV), 1945 (Box 14 (Oversize), Folder 337)